http://www.a2zuniforms.com/privacypolicy

HOMEBrands Brands A-DActivate by Med CoutureAustinBarco OneBarco One TeamBarco WellnessBarco WhitesCeleste SteinCherokee MedicalCherokee WorkwearDickiesBrands E-LElleGrey's AnatomyGreys Anatomy ActiveGreys Anatomy EdgeGreys Anatomy ImpactGreys Anatomy SignatureHeartsoulICULandauLittmannBrands M-PMc2Med CoutureMed Couture AccentsMed Couture BoutiqueMed Couture EnergyMed Couture TouchMed-ManMedlineMotion By BarcoNurseonalityPeachesBrands R-ZRoth WearScrub HQSkechersSmittenTherafirmTooniformsUrbaneScrub Tops Scrub TopsAll Scrub TopsAll Women's TopsAll Unisex TopsAll Mens TopsBarcoBarco One TopsWellness TopsGrey's AnatomyGrey's Anatomy TopsMaternity TopsActive TopsEdge TopsImpact TopsSignature TopsKnit ShirtsSkechersScrub TopsKnit ShirtsCherokeeCherokee Medical TopsDickies EDSDickies GenuineLandauLynxSmittenUrbaneMedlineScrub TopsMed CoutureSolid Scrub TopsPrint TopsMc2 TopsAccents TopsEnergy TopsTouch TopsActivate TopsActivate Tee ShirtsPeachesScrub Pants All Scrub PantsAll Scrub PantsAll Women's PantsAll Unisex PantsAll Men's PantsBarcoBarco One BottomsWellness BottomsGrey's AnatomyActive BottomsAll BottomsEdge BottomsImpact BottomsSignature BottomsSkechersSkechers BottomsCherokeeAll PantsDickies EDSDickies GenuineHeartSoulLandauLynxSmittenUrbaneMedlineScrub PantsMed CoutureMed Couture PantMc2 PantEnergy PantTouch PantActivate PantScrub Jackets Scrub JacketsBarcoBarco One JacketsBarco One Warm Up / SweatshirtsGrey's AnatomyEdge Jackets & BlazersGrey's Anatomy Jackets & BlazersGrey's Anatomy Warm Up / SweatshirtsImpact Jackets & BlazersSignature Warm Up / SweatshirtsSkechersSkechers Warm Up / SweatshirtsCherokeeJacketsWarm Up JacketsLandauSmittenUrbaneMedlineScrub JacketsMed CoutureMed Couture Warm UpTouch Warm UpLab Coats All Lab CoatsAll Lab CoatsAll Women's Lab CoatsAll Men's Lab CoatsAll Unisex Lab CoatsLab Coats by BrandBarco One Jackets & BlazersGrey's Anatomy Lab CoatsGreys Anatomy Impact Jackets & BlazersGreys Anatomy Signature LabcoatsICU Lab CoatsLab Coats by BrandBarco One TeamCherokee Lab CoatsMed Couture Boutique Lab CoatMed Couture Lab CoatsMed Couture Mc2 Lab CoatMedline Lab CoatsEmbroidery
Privacy Policy
We take the privacy of your personal information seriously. This Internet Privacy Policy describes the measures we take to help ensure the security of information collected through our Web sites.
How Personal Information is Collected and Used
We only collects personal information that you voluntarily submit through our Web sites. This may include information such as your name, street and e-mail addresses, and telephone number. We do not automatically collect personal information without your knowledge.
Uses of Personal Information
When you submit personal information to us, you will be asked to decide how we may use your information. Unless we specifically tell you otherwise before you submit personal information, we will only use it to:
Respond to your questions or comments
Better understand your purchasing habits and needs
Help us understand how we can improve our products, services, and Web site
Inform you about special promotions
Contact you to ask for your opinion or willingness to participate in certain events
Limiting the Use of Your Information
If you submit personal information to us, you have two options:
You may choose to allow us to use the personal information for any of the purposes described under the "Uses of Personal Information" section of our Privacy Policy. This is called the "Opt-In" choice.
You may choose to restrict our use of your information to a specific application, such as answering your question about a product. This is called the "Opt-Out" choice.
These options give you the opportunity to control the usage of your personal information by "opting out" of our systems.
Use of Cookies
To improve your visit to our sites, we may use "cookies" to obtain non-personal information (cookies are text information files that your browser places on your computer when you visit a Web site). We may aggregate this data to analyze the viewing habits of our site visitors, but it will not be associated with any personally identifiable data.
Sharing Your Personal Information With Others
We will not use or share your personal information in ways unrelated to the uses described above unless we provide you with prior notice and give you an opportunity to change your usage preferences.Unless you give us prior consent, we will not trade, sell, or share your personal information with any person or entity other than [Retailer Name], our affiliates and representatives, unless required by law or as disclosed to you before the information is collected.For certain promotions or product requests, we may share your information with an outside company for the sole purpose of fulfilling your order. These companies are carefully selected by us and also take the protection of your personal information seriously.
Access to Your Information
To modify your personal information, contact us at [Retailer Primary Email ] We will make every effort to respond to your requests in a timely manner.If you have already submitted personal information to [Retailer Name].com, you may opt-out of the company's future use of that information by sending an e-mail to [Retailer Primary Email ]. Upon receiving your request, we will delete your personal information from our records.
Security of Your Information
The security of your personal information is very important to us. We use appropriate technical and managerial procedures to protect your personal information and prevent its disclosure outside of us. Only those authorized by us will be granted access to your personal information.In addition to careful consideration about what information you share and who you share it with, we recommend that everyone develop good security habits. These include protecting and regularly changing your password, using computer virus protection, logging off when you finish using your computer, and considering the use of file or email encryption programs.
E-mail Preferences
[Retailer Name].com offers you the opportunity to choose whether or not you prefer to receive marketing materials via e-mail by sending us notice at [Retailer Primary Email]. You may update this preference at any time. Please allow us sufficient time to process your change of preference.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may amend this Internet Privacy Policy from time to time. Please check back for updates.
